Jeetu Valecha



Adobe Certified Associate
Visual Communication using Adobe Photoshop CS5

Address:

8/3, New G Ward, Nr. Shivam apartment, Kuber Nagar, Ahmedabad, Gujarat, 382340

Phone: +91-8000424662

Email: <u>ieetuvalecha@yahoo.com</u> Website - jeetuvalecha.weebly.com

Skype ID: jeetuvalecha

Summary

Accomplished Graphic Designer offering 9 years of experience working with various industry clients. Demonstrated success in project management, team leadership and schedule coordination. Fluent in Adobe Creative Suite software.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Illustrator

- Creative design
- Photoshop
- Service-focused

Experience

Senior Graphic Designer – Marketplace (Amazon, Etsy, eBay, Walmart) 08/2019 till date Caterpillar Signs, Ahmedabad

- Create designs, concepts, and sample layouts based on knowledge of layout principles and aesthetic design concepts for Amazon Listings, social media, Print Banners, Fabric, Apparels etc
- Design graphic artwork for use in advertising, ad layouts, packaging, promotional, banners/signage, amazon product listings mockups and other marketplaces like wayfair, ebay, etsy
- Confer with clients to discuss and determine layout design.
- Develop graphics and layouts for product illustrations, company logos, and Internet websites.
- Handle the team of 10 Designers and distribute the work according the requirements.
- Review all final layouts produced by the designers and suggest improvements as needed.
- Maintain archive of images, photos, Fonts or previous work products.
- Prepare notes and instructions for workers who assemble and prepare final layouts for printing.
- Draw and print charts, graphs, illustrations, and other artwork, using computer.
- Study illustrations and photographs to plan presentation of materials, products, or services.
- Research new software or design concepts.
- Mark up, paste, and assemble final layouts to prepare layouts for printer.
- Produce still and animated graphics for on-air and taped portions of television news broadcasts, using electronic video equipment.

Amazon Store Links

https://www.amazon.com/s?k=BANNER+BUZZ+MAKE+IT+VISIBLE

Covid 19 - Related Designs

https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0861JXHBD

https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B08614ZRYR

https://www.amazon.com/dp/B08769238

https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0868RRSSK

Wallpapers

https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B086WCKRJY

Websites <u>www.bannerbuzz.com</u> <u>www.coversandall.com</u>

Production Artist - 12/2014 to 04/2018

Vistaprint Technology, Ahmedabad, Ahmedabad www.vistaprint.com

- Design complex graphics and animation, using independent judgment, creativity, and computer equipment.
- Make objects or characters appear lifelike by manipulating light, color, texture, shadow, and transparency, or manipulating static images to give the illusion of motion.
- Create basic designs, drawings, and illustrations for product labels, cartons, direct mail, or television.
- Develop briefings, brochures, multimedia presentations, web pages, promotional products, technical illustrations, and computer artwork for use in products, technical manuals, literature, newsletters.
- Implement and maintain configuration control systems.
- Handled 3 process simultaneously (Premium Finish, Single Color and Color Strong)
- Handled the problem management process at initial level.

Graphic Designer - 01/2013 to 12/2014 **Radiance Neon, Ahmedabad**.

· Create designs as per Customer Requirement

Education

CHM COLLEGE - 2000 Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Certifications

Sequence Animation Academy 2012